Oh I want you to shake that monkey. What's my favorite word? Why you gotta say it like short?
The word is
fuck nigga
You're a piece of shit
Dead ass. When Amanda start dancing, we was looking at that dead ass. Tonight's blebate topic is
That shit right there is in yo DNA. Yo daddy drank that shit. You didn't land on Plymouth Rock
You landed on that bottle top the hyphy movement the Mac MC hammer
They gonna hit the typewriter across the stage
Would the three athletes be this is a woman who risked her life?
crossing state lines
I'm gonna go with Harriet Tubman
tonight's master Blacksburg is
Mr. Fabi Davis jr
And you gonna put the L on me baby in my case the L stands for too long nigga
I don't drop it